https://shopteasdale.com/pages/privacy-policy#california_privacy

POLICY
Effective Date: This policy was updated and became effective on 4/15/20
This Teasdale Foods, Inc. (“Teasdale”) privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) applies to any websites, online services, and other interactive features or downloads that post a link to or include this Privacy Policy, whether accessed via computer, mobile device or otherwise (collectively, the “Site” or “Sites”). This Privacy Policy only covers information collected online and offline.
Please review this Privacy Policy carefully. Please also review the Terms of Use which governs your use of the Site. Please note that certain features or services discussed in this Policy may not be offered through the Site at all times.
By accessing, using, or otherwise interacting with any part of the Sites, or by otherwise providing information to us, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy and the applicable Terms of Use, which govern your use of the Sites. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE APPLICABLE TERMS OF USE, DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE SITES OR PROVIDE PERSONAL INFORMATION TO US.
TABLE OF CONTENTS
INFORMATION COLLECTION
Information You Provide Directly to Teasdale
User Content Submissions
Information Collected Automatically
Social and Platform Integration
Information We Receive from Third Parties
HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
HOW WE MAY SHARE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED
When You Consent To Sharing Or Request That We Share Your Information
Third Parties Providing Services On Our Behalf
Administrative and Legal Reasons
Business Transfers
Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions
Employment Applications
THIRD PARTY ANALYTICS PROVIDERS, AD SERVERS AND SIMILAR THIRD PARTIES
YOUR MARKETING CHOICES AND UPDATING YOUR ACCOUNT
HOW WE RESPOND TO DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS
SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
THIRD PARTY CONTENT, LINKS TO OTHER SITES, AND TEASDALE CONTENT FOUND OUTSIDE OF THE SITE
CONSENT TO TRANSFER OF DATA
CHANGES TO OUR POLICY
CONTACT INFORMATION
NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS
California Privacy Notice
California Residents – Your California Privacy Rights
NOTICE TO NEVADA RESIDENTS
INFORMATION COLLECTION
We collect information from you directly, automatically when you visit the Sites, and sometimes from third parties. Some of this information may be considered “personal information” under various applicable laws. We consider information that identifies you as a specific, identified individual to be personal information (such as contact information), and we treat additional information, including IP addresses and cookie identifiers, as “personal information” where required by applicable law. And, if we combine information we consider to be non-personal with personal information, we will treat that combined information as personal information under this Privacy Policy and as required by law. Note that we may de-identify personal information so that it is non-personal, such as aggregating or converting it to a code, sometimes using a function commonly known as “hash”. We will treat de-identified information as non-personal to the fullest extent allowed by applicable law.
The Sitesare for general audiences and are not intended for use by anyone younger than the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals younger than age 18.
Information You Provide Directly to Teasdale
We may ask you to provide information directly when you interact with us, such as when you sign up for our marketing emails, including contact information(such as your full name,email address, street address, and telephone number and other information, such as demographic information (for example, your gender, birth day and month, or similar information) andinformation about your preferences and interests.The Sites may also allow you to purchase products directly from us, in which case we may ask you to provide payment information (such as credit and debit card number and other associated card information), as well as shipping and billing information (which may be processed by the third party provider that runs our online store, or by other third party payment processors, depending on your preferred payment method at checkout).
User Content Submissions
The Sites may provide you the opportunity to participate in posting content publicly, such as reviews or in connection with a sweepstakesorto submit or post photographs, videos, questions, reviews, comments, suggestions, or other content (collectively, “User Content”).
Note that anything you choose to submit or publicly post to the Sites may be public— others will have access to your User Content and may share it with third parties. If you choose to voluntarily disclose personal information, that information may be considered public information and the protections of this Privacy Policy will not apply.
Any User Content you submit is subject to our Terms of Use, and may be used by Teasdale in whole or in part for its business and marketing purposes (including in connection with advertising, publicity, and promotional activities) and may be published online or offline (including, without limitation, on the Sites or any format currently existing or later developed).
Information Collected Automatically
In addition to any personal information or other information that you choose to submit to the Sites, we and our third-party business partners (including any third party service providers or third party content, advertising, and analytics providers) may use a variety of technologies that automatically or passively collect certain information about your use of the Sites whenever you visit or interact with the Sites (“USAGE INFORMATION“). Usage Information may include the browser and operating system you are using, the URL or advertisement that referred you to our Sites, the search terms you entered into a search engine that lead you to our Sites (if applicable), all of the areas within our Sites that you visit, and the time of day you visited the Sites, among other information. We may use Usage Information for a variety of purposes, including enhancing or otherwise improving the Sites and our products and services. In addition, we automatically collect your IP address or other unique identifier (“DEVICE IDENTIFIER”) for any computer, mobile phone or other device you may use to access the Sites. A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your device used to access the Sites, and our servers identify your device by its Device Identifier. In some cases, Teasdale may infer your device location based on your IP address or similar information.
The methods used to collect Usage Information may include the following:
COOKIES AND LOG FILES. A cookie is a data file placed on your computer or other device when it is used to visit the Sites or otherwise access our online content. Cookies may be used for many purposes, including, without limitation, remembering you and your preferences, tracking your visits to our web pages, and facilitating your check-out and purchases. We use both session and persistent cookies (which remains on your computer after the browser has been closed).
You may set up your computer to reject cookies by the privacy settings for your web browser although, in that case, you may not be able to use some of the features on our Sites. For further information on cookies, visit www.allaboutcookies.org.
Certain web browsers and browser add-ons, such as Adobe Flash, may provide additional local data storage mechanisms. For example, a Flash cookie is a data file placed on a device via the Adobe Flash plug-in that may be built into or downloaded by you onto your device. Flash cookies may be used for various purposes, including, without limitation, enabling a Flash feature and remembering your preferences. Most browsers provide you with the ability to disable or decline cookies and local storage. You will need to check your browser’s settings for further information. For more information about Flash and the privacy choices Adobe offers, visit http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html.
WEB BEACONS. We may use web beacons (small graphic images or other web programming code, also known as “1×1 GIFs” or “clear GIFs” or “pixel tags”) and similar technologies on our Sites and within our communications to you. Web beacons can recognize certain types of information on your computer such as cookies, the time and date a page is viewed, and a description of the page where the web beacon is placed. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to the Sites, to monitor how users navigate the Sites, to count how many e-mails that were sent were actually opened or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed and to improve your experience on the Sites, including to provide you with content customized to your interests. Our web beacons may collect some contact information (for example, the email address associated with an email message that contains a web beacon).
EMBEDDED SCRIPTS. An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Sites, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your device from our web server or a third party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Sites, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter. In addition, we may use a variety of other technologies that collect Usage Information and similar information for security and fraud detection purposes and to enforce our intellectual property rights.
Social and Platform Integration
Functionality on the Sites may permit interactions between the Sites and third-party interactive or social services (“Social Networking Features”). Examples of Social Networking Features include enabling you to “like” or review a product on our Sitesor to “like” or “share” our page or post on our page on a third-party service; to automatically or selectively show your social media posts on the Sites; and to otherwise connect the Sites to a third-party service. If you choose to share content or to otherwise post information through the Sites to a third-party service, or vice versa, that information may be publicly displayed. Similarly, if you post information on a third-party service that references us (for example, by using a hashtag associated with us in your post), your post may be published on the Sites or otherwise in accordance with the terms of that third party.
Also, both we and the third party may have access to certain information about you and your use of the Sites and the third-party service. These third-party social networking companies may collect information about your visit to our Sites through the Social Networking Features we have integrated into the Sites.Note that through the Social Networking Features, these third party social networking companies may be able to collect certain information about your visits to the Sites regardless of whether or not you affirmatively interact with the Social Networking Feature and whether or not you are logged into (or have) an account with the social networking company.
In addition, we may receive information about you if other users of a third-party service give us access to their profiles and you are one of their “connections” or information about you is otherwise accessible through your profile or similar page on a social networking or other third-party service.
If you submit User Content or use Social Networking Features, including posting on our page within a third party service, we may publish that information or content online or offline, including in connection with our advertising, marketing, publicity, and promotional activities, as further described in our Terms of Service.
The information we collect in connection with Social Networking Features is subject to this Privacy Policy. The information collected and stored by the third party remains subject to the third party’s privacy practices, including whether the third party continues to share information with us, the types of information shared, and your choices with regard to what is visible to others on that third-party service.
Information We Receive from Third Parties
We may receive information about you from other third parties. For example, we may partner with a third party for a sweepstakes or promotion, and your information may be shared in connection with your entry.We may also work with third party data providers to receive more information about our customers, such as contact or demographic informationin order to provide you with information, services, or products you have requested, to tailor content, to offer you opportunities to purchase products that we believe may be of interest to you, and for other purposes.
HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
Teasdale may use information it collects, including Personal Information and Usage Information, to: (1) allow you to participate in features we offer and to provide related customer service; (2) to process transactions and send you confirmations and receipts; (3) to process account registration, such as by verifying your email address;(4) tailor and target content, recommendations, advertisements, and offers we display to you, both on the Sites and elsewhere online; (5) send you marketing communications; (6) understand how you use our products and services, to improve the Sites, our products, and services, and for other internal business purposes; (7) contact you with regard to your use of Teasdale products and services, the Sites, and, in our discretion, changes to the Sites’policies; (8) recognize you across the Sites and devices; (9) operate and protect our Sites from errors, misuse of the Sites, fraud, any criminal activity, and other illegal activities or activities that violate our terms and policies, detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies; or (10) as disclosed at the time you provide your information or otherwise with your consent.
HOW WE MAY SHARE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED
Teasdale may share non-personal information, such as aggregate user statistics, hashed or otherwise de-identified information, and Usage Information, with third parties. However, Teasdale does not share your personal information with unaffiliated third parties for their marketing purposes without your consent (which may consist of offering you the opportunity to either opt-in or opt-out of such sharing).We may share the information we have collected about you as disclosed at the time you provide us with information or with your consent, and as described in this Privacy Policy, including:
WHEN YOU CONSENT TO SHARING OR REQUEST THAT WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION
The Sites may contain registration forms or other features that provide you the ability to opt-in or opt-out of sharing information about you with one or more third parties (for example, in order for a third party to send you special offers or coupons). If you agree at that time to have your personal information shared, your personal information will be disclosed to that third party (or parties) and will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of that third party. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of third parties, and, if you later decide that you no longer want to receive communications from a third party, you will need to contact that third party directly. You also may request, sometimes through your use of social media or other interactive feature, a widget or third party application, that we share information about you or your use of the Sites with a third party, and we will typically do so under those circumstances.
THIRD PARTIES PROVIDING SERVICES ON OUR BEHALF
We may work with third party organizations or individuals to perform services on our or your behalf including processing transactions and fulfilling orders, providing customer service, sending communications, providing marketing assistance and data processing or enhancement, website usage analytics, document management, office services, or other administrative services. We may provide third parties with access to user information in order for them to perform certain services for you or on behalf of Teasdale.
ADMINISTRATIVE AND LEGAL REASONS
We may transfer and disclose user information to third parties: (i) in the event we are required to respond to subpoenas or other legal process or if in our opinion such disclosure is required by law; (ii) at the request of governmental authorities or law enforcement conducting an investigation or otherwise to cooperate on an investigation on public safety or into claims in intellectual property infringement; (iii) to fulfill your requests; (iv) to protect the integrity of the Sites; (v) to protect and/or defend the Terms of Use or other policies applicable to the Sites or to protect the personal safety, rights, property or security of Teasdale or any individual, including for fraud prevention; (vi) in an emergency, to protect the health and safety of our users or the general public. We may also use Device Identifiers, including IP addresses, to identify users, and may do so in cooperation with copyright owners, Internet service providers, wireless service providers or law enforcement agencies in our discretion.
BUSINESS TRANSFERS
Teasdale also reserves the right to disclose and transfer all information related to the Sites: (i) to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of the Sites or one of our databases; or (ii) in connection with a corporate merger or joint venture, acquisition, consolidation, restructuring, bankruptcy, the sale of all or a portion of ownership interests, assets, or both, or other company change, including, without limitation, during the course of any due diligence process.By providing your personal information, you agree that we may transfer such information to the acquiring entity.
SWEEPSTAKES, CONTESTS AND PROMOTIONS
We may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (“Promotion”) that may require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to the terms, conditions or official rules that govern that Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the promotion to use your name, voice, likeness or other indicia of persona in advertising or marketing materials. If you choose to enter a Promotion, personal information may be disclosed to third parties (including, without limitation, a co-sponsor) or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, including, without limitation, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law or permitted by the promotion’s official rules, such as on a winners list.
THIRD PARTY ANALYTICS PROVIDERS, AD SERVERS AND SIMILAR THIRD PARTIES
We work with network advertisers, ad agencies, analytics providers, and other advertising partners to serve Teasdale advertisements online, on our Sites and elsewhere online.In connection with serving content and providing analytics and advertising services, third parties may collect certain information about your visits to this or other web sites, and we may receive information regarding the use of the Sites and the effectiveness of our advertisements. These third parties may set and access their own tracking technologies on your device (including cookies and web beacons) and may otherwise collect or have access to information about Usage Information, including your visits to and activity on the Sites as well as other web sites or online services. Some of these parties may collect personal information from you over time when you visit the Sites or other websites and services. Cookies and web beacons used by us and on the Sites, including those set by third party network advertisers, may be used to, among other things, target advertisements, prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times and to conduct research regarding the usefulness of certain advertisements to you. We may also share information, typically information that is non-personal, Usage Information, aggregated or de-identified or hashed information with third party advertising companies for the purpose ofserving you with relevant advertising on and off the Sites, and to allow others to do so.
Your Advertising Choices
While we may use a variety of companies to perform advertising and analytics services, some of these companies are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) or the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. You may want to visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp, which provides information regarding targeted advertising and the “opt-out” procedures of NAI members. You may also want to visit or http://www.aboutads.info/choices/[Link], which provides information regarding targeted advertising and offers an “opt-out” by participating companies in the DAA Self-Regulatory Program. You may also learn more and make choices about interest-based advertisements from participating third parties at the Canadian DAA online choice page at http://youradchoices.ca/choices. If you are a California resident, please see our “California Privacy Notice” for more information about your rights.
We may use Google Analytics, which uses cookies and similar technologies to collect and analyze information about use of the Sites and report on activities and trends. This service may also collect information regarding the use of other websites, apps, and online resources. You can learn about Google’s practices by going to www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/ and opt out of them by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Please note opting out through these mechanisms does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads while online.
YOUR MARKETING CHOICESAND UPDATING YOUR ACCOUNT
You may opt out of receiving marketing e-mails from Teasdale by following the opt-out instructions provided to you in those e-mails.
Please note that we reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to your use of the Sites (for example, policy updates, service announcements, or communications relating to your use of the Sites) and these administrative or transactional account messages may be unaffected if you opt-out from marketing communications. You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of the information you submit to us.
You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of information you submit to us, such as your contact information. You may update the information you have provided to us by logging into the “Account” setting or similar page on our Sites. Teasdale will make good faith efforts to make requested changes in our then active databases as soon as reasonably practicable. Note, however, that information may persist internally for administrative purposes and that residual data may remain on backup media or for other reasons.
If you sign up to receive SMS or MMS messages that may be offered through the Sites, you may unsubscribe from any text messages received by replying “STOP.”
We may, with your permission, send push notifications to your device through a mobile application. You may opt-out of receiving these types of messages at any time by turning push notifications off in your device settings.
HOW WE RESPOND TO DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS
Note that your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a “Do Not Track” signal to websites and online services you visit. There is no consensus among industry participants as to what “Do Not Track” means in this context. Like many websites and online services, Teasdale currently does not alter its practices when it receives a “Do Not Track” signal from a visitor’s browser except as specifically required by law. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” please visit http://www.allaboutdnt.com.
SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Teasdale takes commercially reasonable steps to help protect and secure personal information. However, please remember that no data storage or data transmission over the Internet, or by other means, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Thus, while we strive to protect your personal data, Teasdale cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. Therefore, you understand, acknowledge, and agree that you transmit certain personal information to the Sites at your own risk.
THIRD PARTY CONTENT, LINKS TO OTHER SITES, AND TEASDALE CONTENT FOUND OUTSIDE OF THE SITES
Third parties may host or serve certain content on the Sites. The Sites may also contain links to third party web sites or features that Teasdale does not control. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use our logo(s) as part of a co-branding agreement, including third parties who may be selling Teasdale products. Third parties whose content appears on the Sites may collect information about you through the use of their own cookies and web beacons, may independently collect or solicit personal information, and may have the ability to track your use of their sites and services. Likewise, Teasdale widgets or other Teasdale content may be included on third parties’ web pages and web sites that are not associated with Teasdale and over which we have no control. Teasdale may collect Usage Information through Teasdale content appearing on third-party sites.
Teasdale is not responsible for the privacy practices employed by any third party, and our hosting of third party content, linking to third party websites, or the appearance of Teasdale content on third party websites does not constitute sponsorship or endorsement of the content or business practices of those third parties.
Teasdale is a United States company and we operate the Sites from the United States. If you are located outside the United States, please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States or other jurisdictions. By using the Sites, or providing us with any information, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to this transfer, processing and storage of your information in the United States and other jurisdictions where the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen.In certain circumstances, your personal information may also be subject to access by and disclosure to law enforcement agencies under the applicable foreign legislation.
CHANGES TO OUR POLICY
To the extent allowed by applicable law, Teasdale may update or supplement this Privacy Policy at any time and any changes will be effective upon posting, unless otherwise indicated. We may also notify you in other ways, such as by email, in our discretion. Your continued use of the Sites after the effective date of the revised Privacy Policy (or other act as specified in the revised Privacy Policy) will constitute your consent to those changes to the fullest extent allowed by applicable law. In the event that there are material changes to the way we treat previously collected personal information, we will provide notice and obtain your consent (opt-in or opt-out), as required.
CONTACT INFORMATION
If you have questions or comments about our privacy policy or our practices, you may contact us by mail at 3041 Churchill Drive, Suite 100, Flower Mound TX 75022. Please note that information submitted to the Sites via a “contact us” or other similar function may not receive a response. We will not use the information provided via these functions to contact you for marketing purposes unrelated to your request unless you agree otherwise.
NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS
CALIFORNIA PRIVACY NOTICE
This California Privacy Notice is effective as of April 15, 2020.
This notice supplements Teasdale’s Privacy Policy and applies only to California residents. This California Privacy Notice sets forth the disclosures and rights for California consumers regarding their Personal Information, as required by the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”).
Terms used in this California Privacy Notice have the same meanings given in the CCPA and the regulations of the Attorney General implementing the CCPA, unless otherwise defined.
INFORMATION TEASDALE COLLECTS
The Personal Information we collect about you will depend upon how you use our Sites or otherwise interact with us. Accordingly, we may not collect all of the below information about you.
We may also collect and/or use additional types of information, and will do so after providing notice and obtaining your consent to the extent such notice and consent is required by the CCPA.
Category of Personal Information Collected
Categories of Sources from which the Information was Collected
Business or Commercial Purpose(s) for which Information is Collected
Categories of Third Parties to whom this type of Personal Information is Disclosed for a Business Purpose
Categories of Third Parties to Whom this Type of Personal Information is Sold
Identifiers
This category includes information such as name, contact information, and online or device identifiers.
We may collect this type of information from:
Consumers,
Cookies and tracking technologies,
Third party service providers,
Third party social media companies,
Third party business partners.
We may use this type of information to:
allow you to participate in features we offer and to provide related customer service;
to process transactions and send you confirmations and receipts;
to process account registration;
tailor and target content, recommendations, advertisements, and offers we display to you , both on the Sites and elsewhere online;
send you marketing communications;
understand how you use our products and services, to improve the Sites, our products, and services, and for other internal business purposes;
contact you with regard to your use of Teasdale products and services, the Sites, and, in our discretion, changes to the Sites’ policies; and
recognize you across the Sites and devices;
operate and protect our Sites from errors, misuse of the Sites, fraud, any criminal activity, and other illegal activities or activities that violate our terms and policies, detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies; or
as disclosed at the time you provide your information or otherwise with your consent.
We may disclose this type of information to:
Third party service providers,
Third parties whose features are integrated on our sites,
Third parties we partner with for contests, sweepstakes, or promotions,
Third party advertising and analytics companies,
Law enforcement or others if required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders),
Third parties as needed to protect and/or defend our legal rights,
Third parties who may acquire your information as a result of a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition,
Third parties when you agree to or request that we share your information with them.
Third party advertising business partners may have access to this data, and this may be considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances.
Any categories of personal information described in subdivision (e) of Section 1798.80
This category includes information such as name, contact information, financial information and online or device identifiers.
We may collect this type of information from:
Consumers,
Cookies and tracking technologies,
Third party service providers,
Third party social media companies,
Third party business partners.
We may use this type of information to:
allow you to participate in features we offer and to provide related customer service;
to process transactions and send you confirmations and receipts;
to process account registration;
tailor and target content, recommendations, advertisements, and offers we display to you , both on the Sites and elsewhere online;
send you marketing communications;
understand how you use our products and services, to improve the Sites, our products, and services, and for other internal business purposes;
contact you with regard to your use of Teasdale products and services, the Sites, and, in our discretion, changes to the Sites’ policies; and
recognize you across the Sites and devices;
operate and protect our Sites from errors, misuse of the Sites, fraud, any criminal activity, and other illegal activities or activities that violate our terms and policies, detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies; or
as disclosed at the time you provide your information or otherwise with your consent.
We may disclose this type of information to:
Third party service providers,
Third parties whose features are integrated on our sites.
Third parties we partner with for contests, sweepstakes, or promotions,
Third party advertising and analytics companies,
Law enforcement or others if required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders),
Third parties as needed to protect and/or defend our legal rights,
Third parties who may acquire your information as a result of a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition,
Third parties when you agree to or request that we share your information with them.
Commercial information
This category includes, for example, information about your transactions with us, reviews you have written, your contacts with our customer service, and your participation in sweepstakes or contests we have offered.
We may collect this type of information from:
Consumers,
Cookies and tracking technologies,
Third party service providers,
Third party social media companies,
Third party business partners.
We may use this type of information to:
allow you to participate in features we offer and to provide related customer service;
to process transactions and send you confirmations and receipts;
tailor and target content, recommendations, advertisements, and offers we display to you , both on the Sites and elsewhere online;
understand how you use our products and services, to improve the Sites, our products, and services, and for other internal business purposes;
operate and protect our Sites from errors, misuse of the Sites, fraud, any criminal activity, and other illegal activities or activities that violate our terms and policies, detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies; or
as disclosed at the time you provide your information or otherwise with your consent.
We may disclose this type of information to:
Third party service providers,
Third parties with whom we have joint marketing and similar arrangements,
Third parties as needed to complete the transaction,
Third parties who assist with our information technology and security programs,
Third parties who assist with loss and fraud prevention,
Third parties who provide professional services to Teasdale
Law enforcement or others if required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders),
Third parties as needed to protect and/or defend our legal rights.
Internet or other electronic network activity information
This category includes information such as details about the hardware and software you use to visit the Sites, areas of the Sites you visit, and login information.
We may collect this type of information from:
Consumers,
Cookies and tracking technologies,
Third party service providers,
Third party social media companies.
We may use this type of information to:
allow you to participate in features we offer and to provide related customer service;
tailor and target content, recommendations, advertisements, and offers we display to you , both on the Sites and elsewhere online;
understand how you use our products and services, to improve the Sites, our products, and services, and for other internal business purposes;
recognize you across the Sites and devices;
operate and protect our Sites from errors, misuse of the Sites, fraud, any criminal activity, and other illegal activities or activities that violate our terms and policies, detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies; or
as disclosed at the time you provide your information or otherwise with your consent.
We may disclose this type of information to:
Third party service providers
Third parties who assist with our information technology and security programs,
Third parties who assist with loss and fraud prevention,
Third parties who provide professional services to Teasdale
Law enforcement or others if required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders),
Third parties as needed to protect and/or defend our legal rights.
Third party advertising business partners may have access to this data, and this may be considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances.
Inferences drawn from any of the information identified above to create a profile about a consumer
These inferences may relate to your perceived interests, preferences, characteristics, or behavior.
We may collect this type of information from:
Consumers,
Cookies and tracking technologies,
Third party service providers,
Third party social media companies,
Third party business partners.
We may use this type of information to:
tailor and target content, recommendations, advertisements, and offers we display to you , both on the Sites and elsewhere online;
understand how you use our products and services, to improve the Sites, our products, and services, and for other internal business purposes;
as disclosed at the time you provide your information or otherwise with your consent.
We may disclose this type of information to:
Third party service providers,
Third parties whose features are integrated on our sites. Third party advertising and analytics companies,
Law enforcement or others if required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders),
Third parties as needed to protect and/or defend our legal rights,
Third parties who may acquire your information as a result of a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition,
Third parties when you agree to or request that we share your information with them.
Third party advertising business partners may have access to this data, and this may be considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances.
EXERCISING YOUR CALIFORNIA ACCESS, DELETION, AND OPT-OUT RIGHTS
California residents have the right to request: (1) that we disclose to you what Personal Information we collect, use, disclose, and sell, including the right to request that we provide to you the specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you in the prior 12 months (“Right to Know”); (2) that we delete the Personal Information we collect about you (“Right to Delete”); or (3) to opt-out from the sale of Personal Information, all subject to exceptions set forth in the CCPA.
More information on each of these rights is below.
Agents
If you are an agent submitting a request on a user’s behalf, please send an email to privacy@teasdalefoods.com with a declaration signed by the individual who is the subject of the request authorizing you to make the request on their behalf.
The written permission must state your full legal name, the full legal name of the individual who is the subject of the request, and needs to be clear about the permission granted.
Alternatively, you may submit a copy of a power of attorney under Probate Code sections 4000-4465. In either case, please also indicate in your email the nature of your request. The consumer’s identity, in addition to your own, will need to be independently verified in order for us to be able to fulfill your request.
We may also ask the consumer to directly confirm with us that they provided you permission to submit a request. Please keep in mind that if we do not receive adequate proof that you are authorized to act on the consumer’s behalf, we may deny the request.
How to Make Request to Know or Request to Delete Verifying Requests Please provide your first and last name, email address you have used to interact with Teasdale, mailing address (if you have provided it), and telephone number (if you have provided it), which we will use to verify your request. We may ask for additional information as needed to fully verify you or your request. If we are unable to verify that the individual submitting the request is the same individual about whom we have collected information (or someone authorized by that individual to act on their behalf), we will not be able to process the request.
Other Important Information:
Request to Know In order to have us provide specific pieces of information, we will require a signed declaration under penalty of perjury that you are the consumer whose Personal Information is the subject of the request.
RIGHT TO OPT-OUT OF THE SALE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION We do not sell your personal information for monetary compensation, but our online advertising practices (and certain analytics or similar activities) may potentially be considered “sales” under the CCPA in certain circumstances.
The Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) offers tools for California consumers to send requests under the CCPA to opt out of the sale of personal information by some or all of the participating companies (https://www.privacyrights.info/).
Additionally, some third-party advertising and analytics companies are members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") or the DAA Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. You may want to visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp, which provides information regarding targeted advertising and the "opt-out" procedures of NAI members. You may also want to visit or http://www.aboutads.info/choices/, which provides information regarding targeted advertising and offers an "opt-out" by participating companies in the DAA Self-Regulatory Program. (Note that these are cookie-based opt-outs. If you disable your cookies or upgrade your browser after opting out, or if you use different computers or browsers, you will need to indicate your opt-out choices across those other computers and browsers.)
You may also be able to limit the access these third-party advertising companies have to information about you when you use our Sites by installing a browser or browser extension that can enable you to block the functionality of some tracking technologies.
Please be aware that utilizing these mechanisms does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads while online.
Users Younger than 16 Teasdale does not knowingly sell Personal Information of minors younger than 16 years of age.
Right to Non-Discrimination for the Exercise of a Consumer’s Privacy Rights California consumers have the right to not receive discriminatory treatment for exercising CCPA rights.
We will not discriminate against you for exercising your CCPA rights.
Contact for More Information
You can contact us for more information by sending an email to privacy@TeasdaleFoods.com.
CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS – YOUR CA PRIVACY RIGHTS
Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, residents of the State of California have the right to request from companies conducting business in California certain information relating to third parties to which the company has disclosed certain categories of personal information during the preceding year for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that a company may comply, as Teasdale does, by disclosing in its privacy policy that it provides consumers choice (opt-out or opt-in) regarding sharing personal information with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes, and information on how to exercise that choice. As stated below in this Privacy Policy, Teasdale provides you choice prior to sharing your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you do not opt-in or if you opt-out at the time Teasdale offers that choice, Teasdale does not share your information with that identified third party for its direct marketing purposes.
If you are a California resident and you have questions about our practices with respect to sharing information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes and your ability to exercise choice, please write to us at the following mailing address: 3041 Churchill Drive Suite 100, Flower Mound TX 75022. You must put the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the subject field of your e-mail or include it in your writing if you choose to write to us at the designated mailing address. You must include your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.
NOTICE TO NEVADA RESIDENTS
Teasdale does not currently sell your covered information as those terms are defined under applicable Nevada law. However, you may still submit an opt-out request and we will honor that request as required by Nevada law if Teasdale were to engage in such a sale in the future. If you are a Nevada resident and would like to opt-out of future sales of your information, you must submit your request to privacy@teasdalefoods.com or call us at 1-877-498-5445. Your request must include your full name, street address, city, state, zip code, and an email address so that we are able to contact you if needed regarding this request. We are not responsible for requests that do not come through the designated request mechanism or do not contain sufficient information to allow us to process your request. You may also be required to take reasonable steps as we determine from time to time in order to verify your identity and/or the authenticity of the request. Teasdale will respond to your request within sixty (60) days either confirming that your request has been processed or indicating that we need an additional thirty (30) days to complete the request.
CLICK TO LEARN MORE ABOUT OUR BRANDS
Use left/right arrows to navigate the slideshow or swipe left/right if using a mobile device
Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
Press the space key then arrow keys to make a selection.
